DAEGWALLYEONG IN MIDWINTER
I wouldn't do Season 2
if it weren't different from Season 1.
NEW KIAN'S B&B
We'll show you now.
This is insane.
- Is that it?
- It's no joke.
- Hello.
- Come on in!
I was waiting for you.
BOSS KIAN84 HAS RETURNED
POWERFUL EMPLOYEE
KIM YEON-KOUNG
SWEET EMPLOYEE
LEE JUN-HO
HARDWORKING YOUNG EMPLOYEE
KAZUHA
We pick up trash as soon as we see it.
We do the dishes right away.
We set an example.
We're getting better.
It's like Our Boss Has Changed.
What a mess.
- No!
Get a grip.
FARTS
The sphincter is loose?
THERE ARE LEAKS EVERYWHERE
I've never seen
other people's poop before in my life.
I stepped on poop. Oh no!
It's coming.
Go! Hurry!
IT'S STILL SO CHAOTIC
Something's always happening
in this damn B&B.
Come here!
- Hit it!
- You punk!
THE EMPLOYEES LOSE IT
Whose pants are these?
What a reality check.
Everyone, let's enjoy!
Stop!
Hey, you can't come back
even if you want to.
Let's go!
Every day is so precious.
Hey! It's no joke!
This is nice.
I knew it.
Have some.
I feel so young.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
- Hello.
THE OPENING OF THE 2ND B&B
A MEETING FOR THE OPENING OF THE 2ND B&B
So what location do you have in mind?
We thought of something like
"Kian's Frozen."
Daegwallyeong or Jeongseon in Gangwon
is really snowy around February.
THE 2ND B&B OPENS IN DAEGWALLYEONG
By when should we…
have the plan?
By the end of November.
- Roughly, at least?
- Yes.
THE GOAL IS TO FINISH A BASIC SKETCH
IN 2 WEEKS
The house…
That's the priority.
How about we go check places out
on Saturdays?
Sounds good.
I think we should keep having
these meetings.
And the employees?
Jin is not available at all
during the winter.
Because of the world tour.
JIN AND YE-EUN CAN'T JOIN SEASON 2
BECAUSE OF CONFLICTING SCHEDULES
That's not good.
We need a superstar.
I'm sure he'll come back.
For Season 3, in summer.
GD would be perfect.
HE WANTS ANOTHER SUPERSTAR
Who else is there?
Has anyone caught your attention lately?
Yeon-koung?
VOLLEYBALL ATHLETE KIM YEON-KOUNG
She's so charismatic, like a general.
SUDDENLY FEELING AFRAID
You can't mess with her.
POLITE
We need to recruit
a lot of good-looking guys.
Or an idol…
If there's someone
you feel uncomfortable with,
that might be good.
Like someone you had a situationship with.
- There's none.
- Or your ex.
HE'S NEVER HAD A SITUATIONSHIP
WITH A SUPERSTAR
I'm curious about the employees.
All right.
It'll be okay, right?
We might get a better idea
when we're there.
DAEGWALLYEONG LOCATION SCOUTING
Let's go check it out.
VISITING THE PLACE FOR SEASON 2
We're like building contractors,
don't you think?
Going around potential construction sites.
I wonder if I'll come up with any ideas.
In Ulleungdo, good ideas came to us,
and we ran it accordingly.
Back then, when I saw the place,
all kinds of ideas came to me.
But I'm not sure this time.
What if I come up with nothing?
In Season 1, I think I did it
without thinking too much.
But since we did it on a floating barge,
people have high expectations now.
So it was hard to come up with something
to meet those expectations.
FEELING THE PRESSURE
TO MAKE IT BETTER THAN SEASON 1
HEADING DEEPER INTO THE MOUNTAINS
WITH A GROWING SENSE OF PRESSURE
AFTER A LONG UNPAVED ROAD
SHAKY
What is this?
THEY ARRIVE AT A SITE IN DAEGWALLYEONG
Where is it?
It's quite nice.
We can build our B&B anywhere around here.
Here?
DEEP IN DAEGWALLYEONG
A LARGE SITE OF ABOUT 33,000 SQUARE METERS
THE SLOPE IS STEEP AND MOUNTAINOUS
The windmills are spinning hard.
The scenery feels dreamlike.
With them spinning up there.
Do cows come here?
Why is there so much poop?
The land is huge.
It's huge.
Come here.
A COW HAS APPEARED
Let's eat.
You won't ram into me, will you?
Want more?
Here.
Hey, come up with some ideas.
THE BOSS IS COUNTING ON A COW
Give me some good ideas, will you?
I can't ride it, can I?
As a means of transport.
DESPERATE
Maybe that side?
HE POSITIONS HIMSELF
AND STARTS SKETCHING
HE DRAWS WITHOUT HESITATION
Will it work?
I'm not sure if it'll work.
DEEP IN DAEGWALLYEONG
KIAN'S 2ND B&B
KIAN'S SECOND IMAGINATION
ALSO BECOMES REALITY
D-100: MEETING
D-86: RECCE
THE FIRST MEETING WITH EMPLOYEES
I'm nervous.
Because of the cameras,
HE'S NERVOUS ABOUT MEETING THE EMPLOYEES
FOR THE FIRST TIME
HE WONDERS WHO THEY ARE
SOMEONE HAS ARRIVED
It's a man.
THE FIRST EMPLOYEE APPROACHES CAUTIOUSLY
I can't look.
HE'S SO NERVOUS THAT
HE CAN'T BRING HIMSELF TO LOOK AT HER
FIRST EMPLOYEE: KIM YEON-KOUNG
Hello.
LEGENDARY VOLLEYBALL SUPERSTAR
VOLLEYBALL EMPRESS KIM YEON-KOUNG
Hello.
Who is it?
- Hello.
Hello.
Actually,
I have met Yeon-koung once or twice
on some shows before.
But we never got to talk properly,
and it was awkward.
HE RECOMMENDED HER, BUT HE FEELS AWKWARD
You don't seem glad.
HIS BACK AGAINST THE WALL
- Why are you not glad?
- It's good to see you.
- Remember we talked casually?
- I don't.
When did we?
You told me
I could talk to you casually.
- So when we met again…
- Where?
GOING ON AND ON
On the third floor of MBC.
I asked,
"I can talk to you casually, right?"
And you said,
"I said you could last time."
I don't remember.
You agreed twice.
- Did I?
- You were born in 1987.
In early 1988.
- Eighty-eight.
- Yes.
And I was born in 1984.
I don't think he likes me.
I do. I thought you were a man earlier.
Because I'm so tall?
Your feet looked as big as mine.
What's wrong with you? Geez.
I'm sensitive about that.
Why? You don't like your feet?
- Got it.
- Okay.
- I mean…
- What?
Why do I feel so awkward?
Well, in Season 1,
weren't you like that with Jin?
So he was practically the leader.
- I mean, it was…
- And I feel like
you'll be like that this time as well.
No way.
Well…
In this B&B…
Yes?
I'm the boss.
Please follow my lead.
Of course I should.
ANOTHER PERSON HAS ARRIVED
Someone's here.
Really?
SECOND EMPLOYEE: LEE JUN-HO
Were you looking for me?
A VERSATILE ALL-ROUNDER
ACROSS MULTIPLE GENRES
It's good to see him again.
Hello.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
It's been a while.
So there's no one I feel comfortable with.
Both of them have appeared on a show
I've worked on for a long time.
So they're familiar faces, but both have…
this strong aura,
so it was hard for me to approach them.
Good to see you.
- It's been a while.
- I brought some pastries.
I thought it'd be nice to talk
while having this.
- Thank you.
- Please.
- Right.
- Have a seat.
This is so awkward.
Gosh, this is…
Thank you for this.
Have you met before?
We have.
- On Home Alone.
- Oh, Home Alone.
- Me too.
- Yes, both of you.
- Right, I met you there.
- Yes.
But never privately.
How old are you?
I was born in early 1990,
so my friends are a year older.
I was born in early 1988. I'm the same.
I also have friends born in 1988.
- Can I talk casually?
- Sure, you can.
Another one's here.
Another one?
THE THIRD EMPLOYEE HAS ARRIVED
- Hello.
Hello.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
I'm Kazuha of LE SSERAFIM.
KAZUHA OF GLOBAL GIRL GROUP LE SSERAFIM
Who?
You don't know me?
I've never met her.
HE DOESN'T KNOW KAZUHA?
LE SSERAFIM.
We've met before.
- We have?
- Yes, we have.
THEY HAVE MET BEFORE?
- Our song, "Eve, Psyche."
- Okay.
You filmed the challenge with us
at our company building.
THEY MET
THROUGH LE SSERAFIM'S SONG CHALLENGE
I remember now!
- You remember?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I didn't remember either.
Both of you didn't remember.
I remembered it recently.
- This is nice.
- Please sit.
So we're the members.
- Great.
- Hello.
FINALLY, ALL OF THE EMPLOYEES ARE HERE
- You're from Japan, right?
- Yes, I am.
Your Korean's so good.
Thank you.
You speak Japanese, right?
- I worked there a bit, so…
- Exactly.
- Right.
- Just a little bit.
- Can you speak it?
- You too, right?
I started learning recently.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
So we can communicate in Japanese.
TODAY
IS OUR
Yes.
- And what?
- Beginning.
Beginning?
IT'S THE BEGINNING
- You're really learning?
- Yes.
I also played in Japan.
Right, as a volleyball player.
Yes, for two years.
- So I can have casual conversations.
- Oh, really?
- Just basics.
We won't be climbing this time, right?
No, we won't.
Or sleeping outside?
No.
What about the fireplace?
The fireplace? It almost killed me.
WORRIED AFTER WATCHING SEASON 1
Are you curious?
You prepared something.
I'll brief you now.
BRIEFING ON KIAN'S 2ND B&B
CURIOUS
BOSS GETS READY FOR A BRIEFING
I'm curious about the house.
I'm excited but…
- Also worried.
- Please.
KIAN'S B&B SEASON 2
BRIEFING
Gosh, finally.
I'm finally doing this
in front of the employees.
I think we began last summer.
We've been having meetings for ideas
to prepare for this
since then.
- It's a B&B, right?
- Yes.
What kind of B&B
will touch our guests' hearts
and also entertain our viewers?
In my opinion,
there are no hopes or dreams.
The world is so cruel.
So cold.
So I'm hoping our B&B
will be full of hopes and dreams.
I'll show you what it looks like first.
KIAN'S 2ND B&B, FULL OF HOPE AND DREAMS
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
It looks like…
KIAN'S B&B
This is the B&B we'll go to.
It looks ordinary.
AN ORDINARY B&B?
Notice anything out of the ordinary?
Isn't something odd?
Can you see?
It's huge.
What?
- First, it's very big.
- How did you know?
The cow is so small.
You sure are sharp.
- Right?
- This is a cow.
If a cow looks that small…
The house is big.
THE HOUSE IS WAY BIGGER THAN A COW
The house…
How big is it?
How big is it, then?
- You see…
- Yes?
Everyone likes a big house.
Fifty-nine square meters,
or 84 m², 112 m².
People strive to move into bigger houses.
They like big land and big houses.
I thought we should offer our guests
the largest B&B possible.
That's why
we built a big house.
But you don't seem to like it.
No.
Jun-ho seems to hate it.
I'm admiring your imagination.
You are?
- Honestly, I never expected this.
- I never imagined it.
Now, how do we open this door
that's so much bigger than a cow?
Right.
So we really need you, Yeon-koung.
A DOOR THAT NEEDS YEON-KOUNG TO OPEN?
PROBABLY YEON-KOUNG?
Unbelievable.
Someone needs to ride on her shoulders.
That's…
We should keep the door open.
No, it'll be so cold.
It'll be about -20°C in Daegwallyeong.
Now, let's say we go into the house.
What does the inside look like?
WHAT'S INSIDE THE WORLD'S BIGGEST B&B?
Like studios near colleges.
It feels youthful. It screams youth.
Here it is.
Our dream, a big house.
This is our B&B.
What?
What happened to it?
I think they're all so big.
The furniture must be ridiculously big.
But we have to climb ropes to go up?
Hold on.
THIS IS HOW BIG IT IS INSIDE
You have to climb the string
of the top to go up.
That's the only way.
I don't think I can.
We'll be sleeping in those boxes?
- The ramyeon boxes are our bedrooms?
- Yes.
RAMYEON BOXES ARE THEIR BEDROOMS
Single room, double room.
- And this…
- Under the TV.
I think four people can sleep here.
The fridge can fit three people.
In the fridge?
EVEN THE FRIDGE IS A BEDROOM
You're so imaginative.
It does feel like a house of hopes
and dreams, childlike dreams.
What's important is the kitchen.
- It's the kitchen, but they're showering.
- On the sink…
We'll use the sink as a jacuzzi.
THE SINK WILL BE USED AS A JACUZZI
- The sink.
- It's that big?
- Like Season 1…
- Yes?
Will we be washing clothes where we swim?
No, we won't.
ACTUALLY, WE WILL
It's a jacuzzi,
but we'll do the dishes there?
And wash clothes.
I don't know.
You don't want to go?
No, it's not that.
No, it's not that. I want to go.
You look down.
- No.
- You look more down.
Guys, don't forget.
- Hopes and dreams.
That'll be all.
That's the end of the briefing.
I see.
You look…
Boss's imagination…
I'm curious to see
how much of it will be realized.
I was surprised by his imagination.
I see.
I'm not sure how we're going
to survive there for nine days.
I'm quite worried, to be honest.
Don't worry about the shape.
- Really?
- I will make it delicious. Don't worry.
COOKING SKILLFULLY
CLEANING SKILLFULLY
Say hello. They're all new.
MASTER OF GROUP LIVING
- She's good.
- Thank you.
Boss, did you wash up?
You keep asking what I did.
- Did you really wash it?
- I did.
- Did you brush your teeth?
- Why do you keep…
- Hello.
YOU CAN SEE HER VOLLEYBALL SPIKE
AS WELL AS SIMILAR SPIKES
Yeon-koung's cycling.
She's amazing, isn't she?
SHE'S IN CHARGE OF VARIOUS WORKOUTS TOO
YEON-KOUNG ADAPTS TO KIAN'S B&B PERFECTLY
Your opinions or ideas.
If you have any suggestions
about how to run the B&B,
please share them with me.
I think
it should be more convenient
when we enter the B&B.
Then there won't be hopes and dreams.
Then I have to keep carrying them?
- It's the biggest house in the world.
- Yes.
We must maintain that vibe.
FOR HOPES AND DREAMS
If they enter easily,
the image hopes and dreams disappears,
and they'll leave without them.
LET'S NOT FORGET ABOUT HOPES AND DREAMS
When we go up,
wouldn't it be better if we could climb
without using our hands?
Then there will be no hopes and dreams.
THE PROTECTOR OF HOPES AND DREAMS
Is there no other way?
No.
- We can't let them lose hopes and dreams.
- Right.
But will they like it?
- They will.
I heard 40,000 teams
applied for it.
A TOTAL OF 40,000 TEAMS APPLIED
TWICE AS MANY APPLICANTS AS SEASON 1
FAMILIES
COUPLES
FOREIGNERS, PEOPLE OF RELIGION
MORE DIVERSE APPLICANTS
WHAT DO THEY EXPECT
FROM KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2?
There's fun in experiencing inconvenience.
When I saw the climbing walls,
I wanted to do it so badly.
No matter how big it is, we can climb it.
There's something romantic
about inconvenience.
I hope it gets bitterly cold.
Like running the marathon topless.
EXTREME COLD THAT WILL TEST THEIR LIMITS
Since it's Daegwallyeong…
I want to scoop the snow and eat it.
Maybe make ramyeon with snow?
Make an igloo and sleep in it.
It's that sort of dream
of rolling around in the snow.
I think youth and romance represent us.
ROMANTIC AND YOUTHFUL GUESTS ARE READY
I trust you guys
to serve the guests well.
One of my regrets from Season 1
was that I noticed the guests
wanted to spend more time
with the employees.
Oh, really?
But there were some guests
I didn't even
get to make eye contact with.
Someone suddenly said they were leaving.
I felt so bad.
I was like, "What?"
I still feel bad.
We should do what they'll enjoy.
THE 2ND B&B PUTS GUESTS FIRST
So we'll only provide dinner, right?
Yes, just one meal per day.
Are you two good at cooking?
Just basic dishes.
I used to live alone
while studying abroad.
So I think I can cook with recipes.
Me too. If I have a recipe,
I can cook it by myself.
Just that much.
We should prepare one each.
I think simple dishes will be better.
Like kimchi fried rice.
- It's simple.
- Sounds good.
I'm from Osaka,
and okonomiyaki is good too.
Okonomiyaki? This?
- Like pancakes?
- Yes.
JUN-HO WILL PREPARE ONE TOO
Anyway, nice meeting you.
Let's do our best.
Sure. I look forward to it.
- Me too.
- We have a month left.
- A month left now.
- A month.
Let's do it.
We should make a group chat.
- Please make one.
- Give me your number.
Can I have your number?
I won't contact you privately.
Okay.
- Make a group chat.
- Right.
THE FIRST MEETING
DAEGWALLYEONG
A POPULAR TRAVEL DESTINATION
AMONG YOUNG PEOPLE
THERE ARE RANCHES
THERE IS WIND
IN DAEGWALLYEONG, THE SNOW KINGDOM
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B OPENS
It's so cold in Gangwon. Interesting.
11:00 A.M.
DAEGWALLYEONG VILLAGE REST STOP
NEAT
You look cool.
Why are you dressed up?
I watched Season 1 again,
and I was always wearing the same clothes.
SINCE IT'S THE OPENING
- Do we meet here?
- Yes.
THE MEETING POINT
Here at last.
Gosh, it's snowing as soon as I'm here.
A LIGHT SNOWFALL
GROWS HEAVIER TO MARK THE OPENING
Gosh, it's so cold.
SNIFFLES
SNIFFLES AGAIN
RUMMAGING THROUGH HIS BAG
THE TOWEL FROM SEASON 1
IT GOES BACK INTO THE BAG
I've been using it for a year.
For the past year.
Whose car is that?
It's a Benz, not a Carnival?
WATCHING CAREFULLY
Who is it?
Oh, it's Jun-ho.
Your good days are over now.
There will be no Benz from now on.
- Hello.
- Jun-ho.
Hello.
- Why are you out in the snow?
- What?
It started to snow when I got here.
- Yes, I was surprised too.
- Right?
Hey, it's cold. You should button up.
I dressed up a bit
since it's the first day.
Your good days are over.
- How have you been?
- What?
- I've been mentally preparing myself.
- Mentally preparing?
- Yes.
Why? For what?
It feels like joining the army.
How about you?
I'm not nervous.
I'm looking forward to it.
But I have no clue.
I feel the same.
- Come on in.
- Okay.
It's freezing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Sit.
It's snowing a lot.
It's freezing.
- Are you all right?
- It's warm in Seoul.
- Are you wearing a suit?
- Yes.
- I was going to wear a tie too.
But it seemed too much.
You look cool today.
We might have to work
as soon as we get there.
THE NEW HIRE HAS SPIRIT
- So I'm prepared for that.
- Right.
It's because it's our first day.
We won't even
think about our clothes there.
Let's enjoy it today.
LOOKING COOL IN EXCHANGE FOR FEELING COLD
- Are you okay?
- It's so cold.
- She's here.
- I couldn't sleep.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Zuha's here.
- Hello.
WITH ZUHA ARRIVING LAST
EVERYONE'S GATHERED
It feels strange.
- Are you feeling good?
- Yes, I am.
Okay, then shall we head out?
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
THEY LEAVE FOR THE B&B
- Who will drive?
- I will.
JUN-HO IS THE DRIVER
It's so spacious.
RIDING IN THE COMPANY CAR
Zuha, do you have leg space?
Yes, it's good.
LEAVING FOR KIAN'S B&B
THAT'S 15 MINUTES AWAY
By the way,
Jun-ho messaged us a few days ago.
Right.
- To wish you a Happy New Year.
- Gosh.
I didn't expect
the chat would be so quiet.
Really?
I thought you'd say something.
I mean, you're the boss.
I'm not the type to reach out first.
You should look after your employees.
- Yes, you should.
- I felt so awkward.
THE BOSS IS TOO SHY
How do you feel now?
- Me?
- Yes.
I think I feel a bit shy.
Shy?
- You feel awkward?
- A bit.
So do I. I feel awkward.
Can I talk casually to you?
Yes, totally.
- Let's all talk casually.
- Yes, let's.
- "Hey, Jun-ho." Like this?
- Yes.
That's good.
I'll talk casually to Zuha.
And you to me, Yeon-koung.
I mean, I think this is
such an unexpected combination.
Anyway, I hope we all get along well.
I hope so too.
DEEP INTO THE MOUNTAINS THEY GO
We're almost there.
- We're here.
- What?
What's that?
Did you draw that?
Over there.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE ENTRANCE
We should be careful here.
KIAN'S B&B
It's beginning now.
But the road looks…
Where are we going?
It's quite a long way from here.
Really?
A SINGLE ROAD IN FRONT OF THEM
Let's go carefully.
- From this point on, it's not on the map.
- I know.
It's not in the GPS.
Can the guests even come here?
Or is it too far to walk from here?
Yes, it's too far.
Is that so?
It won't be easy to come here.
How are the guests supposed to come here?
It's so far.
This is absurd, Kazuha.
- It's there. I can see it.
- It's there.
I can see the B&B.
- That's it?
That must be it.
- This is crazy.
- That's it?
A HOUSE CAN BE SEEN IN THE DISTANCE
- But it's not that big.
- Right.
- Didn't you say it was huge?
- Is it?
It's because it's far away.
- Really?
- It's big up close?
Once you're close…
It's really big?
Let's bring our stuff now.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE PARKING LOT
PARKING LOT, KIAN'S B&B
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Be careful, Zuha. Need help?
THEY WALK DOWN THE PATH TO THE B&B
Follow the footprints, or you'll slip.
This feels so strange.
It looks like an illusion.
- Hey, the house is getting bigger.
- What?
- It is.
- Yes.
The house is getting bigger!
It's getting bigger!
It's so big.
How did they build this?
Hey, the door really is huge.
- We really need to get on your shoulders.
- I know!
Actually, when they see this,
I hope they think it's nothing special.
See this cow next to it?
It's not a dog, it's a cow.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN ORDINARY HOUSE
"Wait, something's not right."
The closer you get, the bigger it gets.
That's how this house looks from outside.
AT THE FOOT OF DAEGWALLYEONG
1,000 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THE HOUSE OF HOPES AND DREAMS STANDS ALONE
KIAN'S SECOND IMAGINATION
HAS BECOME REALITY HERE
Goodness, the door's huge!
It really is huge.
- Wait.
- It's amazing.
- It's huge.
- It's awesome up close.
I really couldn't tell from afar.
What on earth?
It's no joke.
KIAN'S B&B
It's big.
It's not real, seriously.
This is the door handle?
192-CM-TALL YEON-KOUNG
TRIES TO OPEN THE DOOR
- Can you reach it?
- No, I can't.
SO CLOSE
Even she can't reach it.
Hey, how do we do this?
I thought the house
would be perfect for me,
but when I got here, I realized it wasn't.
IT'S HARD EVEN FOR YEON-KOUNG TO OPEN IT
5 M-HIGH DOOR
ABOUT 2.6 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
THIS HUGE DOOR IS THE ONLY ENTRANCE
Can she open it if she jumps?
Hey, how do we do this?
So do we have to open it every day, then?
WE HAVE TO OPEN THIS DOOR EVERY DAY?
- If I hang from it…
- Yes.
- You pull it down.
- I just need to pull it down?
I think Jun-ho's going to give it a try.
ABOUT TO GRAB THE DOOR HANDLE
- Will it work?
- Be careful.
HESITATES
I don't think I can reach it.
- It's so high.
- Let's go.
But can he…
THE DOOR DIDN'T EVEN BUDGE
Hold on.
Just hanging from it doesn't work.
- You have to pull it hard.
- Pull it?
How?
Pull it down.
JUST LIKE OPENING A REAL DOOR
I think someone should
get on my shoulders.
- Should we do that?
- Yeah.
TRIES GETTING ON HIS SHOULDERS
- Will you be okay?
- Or how using a truck and getting on top?
- All right.
- One, two, three.
One, two, three.
Okay.
- Okay.
- I got it.
- Turn it and…
- Pull.
Is it working?
Yes. Move back now. Yes.
IT OPENED
Okay. It opened.
THE PAIR OPENED IT
Let me down.
- Are you okay?
- I'm good.
THEY CAN FINALLY ENTER
- This is insane.
- It's huge!
The interior is insane.
What?
It's like a theme park.
- Let me see.
- Boss!
It'll be so fun.
- What is this?
- "Welcome."
Come on in.
It's amazing.
- The TV.
- That's the TV?
- Is that it?
- Yes.
But the TV stands out so much.
It's at the center.
This is awesome.
They built them this big?
This is incredible.
We experience
a lot of accommodations in life.
If we make a room really big,
it will be the biggest room
the guests will ever stay in.
And I wanted the room
to feel like a friend's studio apartment…
WITH CLASSIC K-STUDIO VIBES
…so they could stay there
as if they were visiting a friend.
INTO THE STUDIO FULL OF HOPES AND DREAMS
It's cold. Let's close it.
LET'S CLOSE THE DOOR FIRST
Let's bring our stuff in.
The door's so inconvenient.
I want to keep it open.
Do we close it?
We'll have to open it again.
- Let's keep it open.
- Yes, let's.
Hold on. Then…
Hold on.
If I close it from outside,
I can't go in.
You can't.
Hey, seriously.
Hey, closing it is the problem.
- Using this?
- This…
I asked them to make this.
A SMALL HOLE
IN THE LOWER PART OF THE DOOR?
MILK DOOR
Doors used to have milk doors.
I think it'd be nice
to have a little hole like that.
All right.
Let's use this to close the door.
USING THE MILK DOOR TO PULL
- I'm closing it.
- That's good. Good idea.
That's smart.
WILL IT CLOSE?
NO, IT WON'T CLOSE
- You have to pull harder?
- Hold on.
- Hold on!
- Harder.
THE DOOR IS CLOSED FOR NOW
Let's leave it like this.
It's still not closed completely.
Guys, let's close it properly.
Since it's the rule.
- For real?
- Yes, for real.
What are you doing?
Not like that. Let's do it right.
NO COMPROMISE
Why did you open it?
Why did you open it again?
Let's close it properly.
Jun-ho, let's do it.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
DO IT BY THE BOOK
On my shoulders.
ON HIS SHOULDERS AGAIN
Be careful.
One, two, three. Okay.
All right.
Harder.
- One, two…
- This should be… Hold on.
Harder!
- That's enough.
- What a relief.
It's so tough.
TOOK 10 MINUTES TO CLOSE
Okay, this is fun!
Let's go in.
Hey, it's warm inside.
THEY FINALLY ENTER THE B&B
People will sleep here too.
Sleep here?
Yes, here too.
- Look at this chair. It's insane.
- It's huge.
A GIANT STUDIO
KIAN'S 2ND B&B
SOFA, FRIDGE
SINK
HANGERS, RAMYEON BOXES
TV
My goodness.
Hey, the fridge…
People can sleep here too.
There's a fridge,
but it's broken,
so people sleep in it.
The house is so big,
everything can be a room.
FRIDGE:
TRIPLE BUNK BED
BOTTOM BUNK, MIDDLE BUNK
Since the house is so big,
everyone's so happy.
TOP BUNK
This is insane.
How do you get up there?
I don't think it'll work
even if you use the sofa.
5 M-HIGH FRIDGE
ABOUT 2.6 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
HOW TO CLIMB THE HUGE FRIDGE
FIX THE DOOR LATCH TO THE FLOOR
CLIMB UP BY STEPPING ON THE COMPARTMENTS
Like this?
HE CONQUERS THE TOP
This is amazing.
The fridge won't be very popular.
You're the one who made it.
- You made it.
- But…
THE BOSS IS OVERWHELMED BY ITS SIZE
MEANWHILE, ZUHA IS…
It's better than I thought.
- It's good?
- Yes.
You can use it, then.
SLEEPING ZUHA IN THE FRIDGE
- Is Kazuha inside?
- Yeah.
How is it?
It's better than I thought.
- Really?
- It's good? Then you use it.
- You use it.
- You sleep there.
ZUHA WINS A SLEEPING SPOT IN THE FRIDGE
No!
It's better than I thought. That's all.
ZUHA'S REVIEW:
JUST BETTER THAN I THOUGHT
Shall we check out the kitchen?
SINK
What about this? What is this?
SINK CABINETS CLOSED SHUT
WHAT IS INSIDE?
This one
is the sink cabinet.
There's a sauna inside.
A SAUNA UNDER THE SINK
THE BOSS PREPARED IT
THE HIDDEN SPACE OF KIAN'S B&B
WHILE DESIGNING THE SINK
We should put a sauna in here.
It was a quick idea,
but the sauna under the sink…
CABINET:
SAUNA
I liked it the most.
I think the guests liked it the most too.
PEOPLE GATHER HERE NATURALLY
THE HOT SPOT OF KIAN'S B&B
- It's well-made.
- This is so nice.
- I love it.
- It's great.
- It's so warm.
- So warm.
Come in.
- It's warm.
- So warm.
- I want to sleep here.
- Awesome.
This is great.
- It should be closed.
- Yes, to keep it warm.
- Keep it closed. And what's this?
- It's much bigger.
- It's the way to the kitchen.
- The kitchen's up there.
- You have to go up?
- Yes.
THE WAY TO THE KITCHEN
This is it.
This is a dishrag.
You must climb it to cook in the kitchen.
DISHRAG:
CLIMBING
Since this house is so big,
you have to climb all the way up.
CLIMB BY HOLDING THE HOLES
- This is it.
- Hold on.
We have to climb it to the kitchen?
Yes.
It's so hard to eat.
What shocked me was the sink.
Because the kitchen was so high.
3 M-HIGH SINK
ABOUT 1.6 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
Shall we go up to the kitchen?
How are you supposed to climb this?
How…
PEEKABOO
Gosh, you have to climb like that?
This is wrong.
THE WRONG VIEW
It looks so wrong.
ARRIVING WITH A GROAN
It's so tough.
Guys, you have to stay on your toes.
I'll go first. Hold on.
Come on up.
Gosh, hold on.
Hold on.
FLUSTERED
Climbing up to the kitchen
was harder than I thought.
We have to climb up
every time we go to the kitchen.
It's quite inconvenient.
THEY ARE ON THE SINK
I'll end up exhausted.
This is the sink.
NOT A SINK
A GIANT WASH BASIN
Does it work? Try it.
"Open."
- It's working.
THE FAUCET WORKS
We don't have to make a jacuzzi separately
since the house is big.
SINK:
JACUZZI
FOR YOUTHFUL ADVENTURE
Handsome and pretty young people
will come, so I prepared a jacuzzi.
A JACUZZI ABOVE A SAUNA
People will use the jacuzzi, right?
I think so. I think they'll love it.
What? We do the dishes here?
We'll ruin our knees
while doing the dishes.
- Yes, do the dishes here.
- You should do it sitting there.
Sit here?
LOOKS PATHETIC
If you do it in this soy sauce dish,
it'll be comfortable.
I thought it'd be nice
if we did the dishes in a soy sauce dish.
SOY SAUCE DISH:
WASH BASIN
- There's rice.
- Right.
- We have rice.
- And the basic…
Seasonings.
If we won't use the stove here,
I should put something here.
A campfire…
A REAL GIANT GAS STOVE
WOULD BE TOO DANGEROUS
You know those portable burners.
We'll use them to cook food.
THE PLACE FOR THE STOVE
HAS BECOME THE COOKING AREA
Is there ice cream in it?
HUGE ICE CREAM
This is awesome.
We need a fridge too.
But it's no fun if it's obvious.
We'll make it look like ice cream.
ICE CREAM:
FRIDGE
- Is it a fridge?
- Yes, a fridge.
My God.
- It's so well-made. Right?
- Seriously.
But…
I'm already so tired.
I love that everything's been made
according to the drawings.
But honestly, I expected it
to be more convenient.
- But not at all.
- Not at all.
But the more convenient they are,
the less memorable.
You already look tired. Are you okay?
HARDSHIP MAKES MEMORIES
I always do this. I tend to walk
into the trap I made myself.
THE TRAP HE MADE HIMSELF
There's another way there.
- There is?
- There's a pole.
I think we can go down here.
I think so.
Actually, depending on your preference,
if you prefer pole climbing,
you can climb the gas pipe.
THE POLE IS BACK
It's so high.
4.4 M-HIGH GAS PIPE
ABOUT 2.3 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
- I can't do it.
- It's scary.
GIVING UP RIGHT AWAY
God, the ways up and down
are both not easy.
- Like this?
- Yes.
My feet hurt so much.
Hey, we have to take them off the hangers.
- What?
- The clothes.
- Why?
- They're comforters.
- They're comforters?
- Yes.
They can use these as comforters.
But they can also use those.
This is the best stay, I think.
Let's say you crash at a friend's place.
"Hey, want comfy clothes?"
"Comfy clothes."
Let's say it's a big T-shirt.
They can use the big T-shirts
as comforters.
T-SHIRTS
COMFORTERS
USE A FRIEND'S T-SHIRT AS A COMFORTER
AND STAY COMFORTABLY
AS IF IT WERE A FRIEND'S PLACE
FOLD THEM NEATLY AFTER USING THEM
THERE ARE ALSO HUGE SOCKS
- How do we get them down?
- How? How do we get up there?
4 M-HIGH HANGER POLE
ABOUT 2.1 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
Like a judoka.
- Climb it.
- We have to climb it?
Yes, you're on the national team.
- You're a national athlete.
- I don't train like that.
Volleyball players don't climb ropes.
- Don't you all do that?
- No.
CAN'T YOU DO IT?
Volleyball players don't climb poles.
AND IN THE CORNER
What are these boxes?
Isn't this a room too?
A SUSPICIOUS RAMYEON BOX
- It's awesome.
- It's so cute.
Hey, this is nice. Nice and cozy.
It's so private.
Isn't this a solitary cell?
A PRIVATE ROOM
What I felt during Season 1 is,
since guests didn't have their own room,
they wanted to rest in a private space.
Then we should create
some private spaces this time.
TAKEAWAY FROM 1ST B&B: PERSONAL SPACE
A ramyeon box?
Yeah, we need a couple ramyeon boxes.
One more here.
RAMYEON BOXES:
PRIVATE ROOMS
Hold on. Then…
This is a room too.
I think it's better.
TOP RAMYEON BOX
It's open here, so…
I want to sleep here.
- You like it?
- Yes.
This one's so nice.
THE TV CABINET IS ALSO A PRIVATE BEDROOM
And the most important thing is the TV.
HOW TO GET TO THE TV
1. CLIMB THE BOX
How do we climb this one?
THE ENTRANCE OF THE TV
- How's it?
- Let's go together.
How do you climb this?
With bare feet?
AND…
HOW TO GET TO THE TV
2. CLIMB THE STRING OF THE TOP
- Push me up.
- You got it? Give me your hand.
How is it?
- You don't want to see?
- I can from here.
It's great.
I'm sure you want to see this.
THEY GO INTO THE TV
You have to see this.
WHAT'S INSIDE THE TV?
Do you see the TV here?
This adds a nice kick to Kian's B&B.
The TV screen opens.
It's a karaoke.
Wow, that's awesome.
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
Inside the TV is like a coin karaoke.
WELCOME
And when the screen opens,
it becomes a stage.
AN ORDINARY TV
TRANSFORMS INTO A STAGE
So I was hoping for singers.
- And you two came.
- Us?
YES, YOU GUYS
- Ta-da.
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE OPENING SOON
- Isn't it nice?
- Wow.
- Like this?
- Like this.
If you want to sing in front of people,
you can sing here.
AUDIENCE SEATING WILL BE AVAILABLE
You agreed to perform, Kazuha.
Alone? Let's do it together.
You singers perform, and so can we.
It's karaoke, after all.
NO PRESSURE
AT KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
And I'm sure
some of the guests will sing too.
- Right.
- They'll want to sing too.
There might be a good singer.
THEY HAVE FINISHED THE TOUR
I think 99.9% of it has been realized.
And I find that incredible.
Wow, did they really make this?
Oh, this is so nice.
It's great.
It was amazing, and it was also so fun.
Wow, this is the gym.
YEON-KOUNG SUGGESTED A GYM BY THE WINDOW
- An exercise bike?
- Yes.
Wait, is this a trampoline?
LAUNDRY BASKET:
TRAMPOLINE
The bathroom's good enough.
It's gotten so much better.
AND THE CABINET BATHROOM
HOW TO USE THE HUGE TOILET PAPER
I like the big toilet paper.
- Isn't this what Zuha suggested?
- Right.
It's amazing.
If we could have a skating rink outside…
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I think it's good enough.
- You're good.
- Yes, it's good.
You're good, Kazuha.
- It's perfect.
- Yes, it's good.
AFTER THE TOUR
Hey, you look so small.
- Do I?
- Yes.
You look so kawaii right now.
KAWAII YEON-KOUNG
THANK YOU
THANK YOU, KIAN
What should we have for dinner?
- Kimchi fried rice?
- Sounds good.
Put grilled pork belly
on top of kimchi fried rice?
Sounds good.
- Then pork belly and kimchi fried rice.
- Okay.
NEXT, THEY HAVE A MEETING
Once the guests arrive,
give them comforters.
And those who have a drink at night,
ask them to sleep on the first floor.
And the fridge,
there are safety belts in there.
Tell them to keep them on.
Those who don't wear belts while sleeping
will be kicked out.
Kicked out?
We should keep an eye on them.
LOOKED AFTER BY THE STAFF
And we'll turn the lights off at bedtime.
Should we set it at 11:00 p.m.?
We have to turn them off,
but they're so high.
LIGHT SWITCH
4.7M-HIGH
ABOUT 2.45 YEON-KOUNGS TALL
Isn't it like training?
EVEN TURNING OFF THE LIGHTS ISN'T EASY
- And since it's the first day…
- Yes.
When the guests are here,
how about we use the sauna or the jacuzzi?
- Together?
- Wouldn't it be better?
- Let's decide after dinner, then.
- Okay.
All together.
FIRST EVENING EVENT
SAUNA
Let's decide our rooms first.
ASSIGNING STAFF ROOMS
I'm thinking of using the box bedroom.
- The top box?
- Yes.
- And Zuha?
- Whichever is fine.
BOTTOM RAMYEON BOX: ZUHA
TOP RAMYEON BOX: YEON-KOUNG
Which one will you use?
Me?
I like the one under the TV.
- Then let's use it together.
- Sure.
TV CABINET: KIAN & JUN-HO
It's so big.
BLOWS HIS NOSE
My forearms are already exhausted.
- In Season 1…
- Yes.
I was in great shape when it was over.
BLOWS HIS NOSE AGAIN
When did you catch a cold?
This morning.
Gosh, it's so cold.
You shouldn't catch it from me.
If you catch a cold too, it'll be so bad.
DON'T CATCH IT FROM ME
- It's okay.
- Still.
Are you sure
you don't want to switch rooms?
It's fine.
Are you sure? I don't mind.
Are you sure?
It's fine.
It's okay.
AFTER THEY UNPACK
This is great.
What time is it? It's 12:00 p.m.
- We haven't even had lunch.
- Right.
THEY LEAVE TO EAT AND SHOP FOR GROCERIES
- Did you put on your seat belts? Good.
- Yes.
Now, let's go.
HEADING DOWNTOWN THAT'S 15 MINUTES AWAY
They'll like it, right?
- Like what?
- Our B&B.
I think they'll be surprised at first.
It'll feel like a theme park.
That's right.
What time do they usually call?
It depends.
- Some come in the evening.
- Right.
Some come during the day.
If a lot come from the start,
- it'll be tough.
- Right.
MEANWHILE
It's snowing a lot.
I'm so excited!
THE FIRST GUESTS ARRIVE IN PYEONGCHANG
AND THE STAFF ARRIVE AT THE RESTAURANT
I'll have the set meal.
- The set meal?
- There's steamed or grilled.
Grilled dried pollack.
I'll have the set meal too.
Dried pollack soup.
One soup and three set meals.
1 DRIED POLLACK SOUP
3 GRILLED DRIED POLLACK SET MEALS
THE BOSS CAUGHT A COLD TRYING TO LOOK COOL
HE SPLITS A NEW PIECE OF TISSUE,
ROLLS THEM,
AND PUTS THEM
IN EACH NOSTRIL
The employees have their own rules.
RULES FOR EMPLOYEES?
Well, we set an example.
We pick up trash as soon as we see it.
- Whoever sees it first.
- Yes.
We do the dishes right away.
Right away.
I think everyone here
will do it proactively.
- None of us are irresponsible.
- I'm sure.
- It looks so good.
- Whose is this?
GRILLED DRIED POLLACK
We'll share it.
DRIED POLLACK SOUP
- Let's share it.
- Enjoy.
Thank you for the food.
It's good.
We have to clean too.
Of course.
- And dust off the comforters.
- Yes.
And we have to keep the jacuzzi clean.
Right. And do the laundry.
CHECKING THINGS TO DO
Darn it, the laundry.
- The laundry…
- Hey, the laundry…
Your nose really keeps running.
The laundry…
You've got a bad cold. Are you okay?
What about the hospital?
- Don't worry.
- That's the spirit.
I want to go to the hospital.
I'm sorry, but why do I have two cups?
2 PAPER CUPS IN FRONT OF YEON-KOUNG
Let's just share them. We'll get closer.
HATING IT
This is mine.
- Are you sure?
- Probably.
THE BOSS'S CUP
YEON-KOUNG'S CUP
THE CUPS WERE SWITCHED
THE BOSS'S CUP
Is the call from a guest?
I have a feeling it is.
Is it?
NERVOUS
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hi.
We're guests at Kian's B&B for today.
- Yes.
- I called you to check in.
I see.
Where are you right now, then?
We're at Daegwallyeong Yangtte Ranch.
Yangtte Ranch?
ALREADY AT DAEGWALLYEONG
So you didn't drive here?
We came by taxi.
By taxi?
- I'll send you the address.
- Okay.
Did you drive here?
ASKING WHAT HE JUST ASKED AGAIN
- Taxi.
Right, taxi.
We'll send you the address soon.
COVERING FOR THE BOSS
WHO'S NOT FEELING WELL
I think you should come
between 3:30 and 4:00 p.m.
1:45 P.M.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
Wait, how many are you?
THE BOSS IS BACK IN ACTION
Two people? Okay, see you later.
- Bye.
Then they don't know about us, right?
- The guests don't know.
- Not yet.
- Right. They don't know about you guys.
- They don't.
You heard a different man's voice, right?
- Yes.
- Try to guess it.
I think he's an actor,
judging by the voice.
- I'm so curious.
- I think he's an actor.
DAEGWALLYEONG YANGTTE RANCH
- Wow, they're so cute.
- So cute.
They're so cute.
So cute.
I'll take a photo too.
Two, three.
HEADING TO KIAN'S B&B WITH HIGH HOPES
We have to cook dinner every day.
I practiced cooking okonomiyaki.
- Really?
- A little.
That's amazing.
You must've been busy, but you did it.
ARRIVING AT THE GROCERY STORE
2:00 P.M.
Thank you.
Hello.
All right. Now…
- Zuha, the ingredients for okonomiyaki.
- Do I only do that?
KIAN & JUN-HO'S CART
MEAT, CANNED TUNA, RAMYEON, SNACKS
YEON-KOUNG'S CART
BANANAS
GREEN GRAPES, BEER FOR GUESTS(?)
PASTA
- Kazuha, you need help?
- Potatoes.
CONFUSED ZUHA
- Potatoes? Check there.
- Where are they?
SHE CAN'T FIND POTATOES
There are sweet potatoes here.
"Potato" is written here.
I can't believe you.
Kazuha. Look, it says "potato."
I'm not Korean.
OKONOMIYAKI INGREDIENTS
POTATOES
Do you know where the yams are?
ASKING AN EMPLOYEE
Do we have yams?
NO YAMS
- We don't have them. Yes.
- Really?
What do I do?
I'm doomed.
Hello?
If there are no yams, what do I do?
ASKING HER MOM FOR HELP
Lotus roots? Okay.
BUYING LOTUS ROOTS INSTEAD
Starch? Okay.
2ND ALTERNATIVE: STARCH
Korean is hard.
These are all starch.
- All of them?
- Yes, starch.
THE STARCH WAS CLOSER THAN SHE THOUGHT
THE PHONE RINGS AGAIN
More guests?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hi.
More guests are coming.
Kian's B&B…
Yes.
- We're guests for today.
- This is bad.
How many are you?
Two people.
- What do we do?
- We're in trouble.
I'll send you the address.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- How many are coming?
- Two.
- Two more. Four, then.
- Yes.
Two men and two women.
GUESTS ON THE 1ST DAY
4 PEOPLE
- It looks so small from here.
- Right.
- It looks small.
- Yes.
I'm scared.
3:00 P.M.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Thank you.
Carry this. It's lighter.
- God! You said it was light.
- It's the lightest one.
You little punk.
You punk!
Gosh, it's heavy.
It's so far.
I think it's between 25 kg and 30 kg.
Is it heavy?
I'm good.
- Do we have to go back?
- Is there more?
ZUHA GOES TO HELP
Why?
Isn't there one more?
Is there more?
No.
Zuha, you just go back.
You won't be of much help.
You should come and organize them.
Why do you not worry about me?
They didn't tell me to come back.
I'm coming to help you.
You can't carry this alone.
One, two, three.
Are you okay?
Just come here, Zuha.
How is it?
JUN-HO HAS COME TO HELP
Carry this and the cabbage in there.
- Just two feel heavy, right?
- No.
Why isn't she opening the door?
- You have to do it.
- I'm so tired.
- Boss, should I carry it?
- What?
We're almost there.
Let's put it down here.
I'll do it.
- How heavy are you?
- I'm heavier than I look.
Let me carry you.
YEON-KOUNG'S SO TALL
- Climb up.
- Wait.
Darn it!
THE SAME AS YEON-KOUNG'S HEIGHT
- She can't reach it.
- She can't.
NOT EVEN CLOSE
- She can't reach it.
- One, two, three.
- You can't?
- I can't.
We can't.
Let's do it.
Are you okay?
- Are you sure?
- This is the last time.
One, two, three.
Okay.
All right. Open.
Pull. It's open.
So why did you have to make it this way?
Hopes and romance.
Hopes and romance, and nothing else.
And nothing else?
This is not right.
We have to take it up to the second floor.
IT'S LAUGHABLE
It's only fun when building it.
Only when I imagined it.
We can leave the snacks down here.
- Only vegetables.
- Yes.
SORTING BOXES FOR THE SINK AREA
Okay, it's done.
HIS COLD HAS GOTTEN WORSE
HE PUTS THE TISSUES IN
Okay.
Why did I build it like this?
I'll try pulling it
with the rope from here.
A ROPE?
It'll be so inconvenient
if everyone has to climb up.
Maybe we can use a rope.
Like a shoelace.
It'll be nice to lift things using that.
Should we try lifting them with this rope?
TIE IT TIGHTLY
- Can you lift it?
- Yes.
- All right.
- I'll pull.
One, two, three!
Wait.
KIAN'S PULLEY
Okay.
Can you lift it?
Can you?
He's doing it.
HE LIFTED IT UP
Okay.
Great.
This is exhausting.
Hey, take it with your hand.
- We should support the bottom.
- Right.
It's done.
Good work.
It's time for them to come.
3:30 P.M.
- It's all ready.
- What?
Is it?
- They can come.
- Okay.
- Soon.
- Hey, the door…
Should we have them open it?
GUESTS HAVE TO OPEN THE 5-M-TALL DOOR?
I want them to experience it.
If they don't know how to open it,
it won't be easy.
Get on someone's shoulders…
I'll send them a message, then.
"You can open the door to come in."
"If it's too difficult,
we'll come get you."
I should close it before they come.
HE CLOSES IT FOR A SURPRISE
What's wrong with this?
Why is the TV…
Why won't it close completely?
Our hopes and dreams will…
HOPES AND DREAMS ARE READY
A LONG WAY DOWN
It's so inconvenient.
I mean…
I can never get used
to this inconvenience.
Kazuha's so cute.
- They're not here?
- No.
- No?
MEANWHILE,
A CAR IS ON THE WAY TO THE B&B
It's so snowy. The snow's piled up.
Hold on, we're going to see them now.
- It doesn't feel real yet.
- I know.
Where is it?
- Is it that one?
- That down there?
Isn't it that?
I think it's that one, right?
Kian's B&B is there.
KIAN'S B&B SLOWLY COMES INTO VIEW
Wow, we're really here.
THE FIRST GUESTS ARRIVE
I'm so excited!
Why's the door so big?
- The door's huge!
- What?
It's so huge!
- It's twice as tall as you.
- I know!
Once we open it,
what if we have to ride something
or crawl around?
Why do I feel so nervous?
I thought it was just a small house.
But it got bigger as we got closer.
And that was a new kind of shock.
"You can open the door and come in.
Thanks for coming."
"You can open the door and come in"?
HOW DO WE OPEN THE DOOR?
How do we open it?
Let's use our brains.
We should be smart about it.
Mr. Kian.
Please open the door.
HOW TO OPEN THE DOOR
1. BEG
MEANWHILE
2. TRY IT THEMSELVES
- I'll try.
- I think you can do it.
Since you're tall.
No, I can't.
No. It's impossible.
How do I…
- You won't open it?
- Wait.
They're still trying.
STILL HOPEFUL
Shouldn't I just lift you up?
- Are you sure?
- I can. I've been working out lately.
No way. You'll get hurt.
Should I open it?
- Yes!
Wow! Yes!
It's opening.
Give me my bag. Sorry.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Goodness!
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Goodness!
- Come on in.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
THE FIRST GUESTS CHECK IN
So we finally meet.
KIM HEE-JEONG, WOO JAE-EUN
As soon as we entered,
the whole place was just gleaming.
The house felt so alive,
it made us feel miniature.
FIRST MEETING WITH THE EMPLOYEES
EXPLOSIVE REACTION
Hello, girls.
Hello.
Oh, my God!
The first reaction is really good.
I'm having a heart attack.
It's a success.
They look like participants
on some dating show.
- They're coming.
- Yes.
THE SECOND GUESTS?
Two gentlemen are coming.
What's that sound?
They're having a blast without us.
THE SECOND GUESTS ARE GETTING CLOSE
Is that it?
- I think they're looking at us.
- I know.
Why is it…
- Here?
- I know, right?
THE DOOR SUDDENLY CLOSES
- Why did they close the door?
- Why… Wait.
FLUSTERED
Hold on. We should close it.
HE CLOSES IT FOR THEM TO EXPERIENCE IT
Hey, not opening the door
for the guests is fun.
- You closed it again?
- What?
- You closed it?
- Yes.
We should let them experience that first.
- Is this for real?
- What…
- How do we open it?
- Should we jump?
- Give it a try?
- You try it.
You do it alone first.
It works.
Let me try.
- They're opening it.
- They are.
They're opening it.
IT OPENED?
We can open it now, no?
I mean, are they monsters or what?
They opened it.
- They opened it. Amazing.
- They opened it.
Hello.
SEO JEONG-WON, YOO DON-HEE
Nice to meet you.
THE SECOND GUESTS CHECK IN
But you have to close it too.
Really?
Come in first.
Carefully.
Be careful.
Good.
- It's done.
- Wow, great.
Welcome.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Welcome to Kian's B&B!
WELCOME TO KIAN'S B&B
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
It's like a studio apartment.
So…
we wanted to let you stay
in the biggest room in the world.
We made a giant version of the typical
studios you find near colleges.
It looks like it.
You can sleep in any room you want.
GUESTS CAN SLEEP ANYWHERE
We made it feel like Badly in Love.
Badly in Love.
This is the sauna.
That's insane.
1ST FLOOR: SAUNA, BATHROOM
And that's the sink,
which you can use as a jacuzzi.
- See those T-shirts over there?
- Yes.
They're comforters.
Take them off and use them.
- But how?
- How do you take them off?
Since you're here, why don't you try it?
Will you try take them off the hangers?
It's a unique experience.
If you feel you can't do it
while trying it, let us know.
Gosh, you can never
experience this elsewhere.
- Should I try pulling it?
- Try.
- This one…
- I think we can.
- Harder.
- Hang from it.
- It'll rip.
- Yes.
Hang from it.
SHAKY
- It'll rip.
- Yes.
I think it's working.
- It's working.
- It worked.
We did it.
You've obtained a comforter.
But it's so heavy.
They did it.
- You can look around.
- Sure.
Make yourself at home.
- This is my home.
- Comfortably.
LAUNDRY BASKET TRAMPOLINE
Open it.
Like this? Hello.
It's something you can only see in dreams.
But they made it real.
It felt carefree and romantic.
It was full of youth.
It feels satisfying when your plan works.
THE BOSS IS VERY SATISFIED
And we should give them this.
Two towels per person?
KIAN'S B&B'S AMENITIES
Here, use these…
- Thank you.
- when you use the jacuzzi or sauna.
Thank you.
CLOTHES FOR THE SAUNA & JACUZZI
SLIPPERS
And two towels per person.
1 TOWEL PER NIGHT
And you can return them with the slippers
when you leave.
If you don't, we'll chase you.
MANDATORY RETURN
- The B&B's gotten better.
- Really?
- Did you watch Season 1?
- Yes.
Really? Great.
Thank you.
We will provide dinner.
And you take care of the rest.
TIME TO DECIDE ON ROOMS
The middle and top bunks.
- The middle and top? Are you sure?
- Yes.
- There are safety belts.
- Belts.
Wear them when you sleep.
SAFETY BELT
Are you students?
- Yes, we just turned 20.
- Just.
SURPRISED
- Yes.
- We're freshmen.
- We just came of age.
- We're adults now.
They're the same age as us.
- Did you graduate, then?
- We did.
- We did. Less than a month ago.
- Not long ago.
- Then you're starting college?
- Yes, soon.
LISTENING CLOSELY
- You must be excited.
- Yes.
Hello.
You haven't decided on your rooms?
JEONG-WON AND DON-HEE PICK THE SOFA
- You don't seem to like it.
- No, no.
Go lie down.
Let me cover you with comforters.
- Sure.
- Let's give it a try.
Are you college students too?
- We're 20 too.
- Yes, we're 20.
- You turned 20?
- Yes.
SURPRISED
They're 20 too.
Nice to meet you.
20-YEAR-OLD GUESTS
As if it's a friend's place.
- This is nice.
- I already feel warm.
- It's so nice.
- Is it okay?
TIGHT
That's so cute.
Don't they look so uncomfortable?
IT FITS THEM PERFECTLY!
You look so close.
- Here.
- Thank you.
It looks like
it was specially made for you.
This is nice.
Gosh, we don't have enough towels.
THE PHONE IS RINGING?
No way.
More guests?
More guests are coming?
There's more?
Hello?
What? English?
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu